viously.com 2019-03-30

# Privacy policy - Viously

Protecting Your personal information is VIOUSLY's priority.

This privacy policy (the « Privacy Policy ») governs your (« Your », « You » as applicable) access and use of VIOUSLY’s website available at the following URL address: [www.viously.com](https://www.viously.com/) (the “Website”), and the services related to and/offered on VIOUSLY’s web hosting video platform (the “Platform”), which is available to creators (the “Creators”) and/or broadcasting partners after registration online and/or by executing an agreement with VIOUSLY (together the “Services”). The Privacy Policy governs the collection and processing of Your data by VIOUSLY and any of its affiliates. 

## 1\. General Information

By accessing and/or using the Services, You, either as an individual or a single entity, hereby fully consent to all terms of the Privacy Policy, and to any provisions of the TOU notably terms related to age restrictions. 

## 2\. Data collection

“Data” shall mean any information indicated by You voluntarily and/or collected by VIOUSLY when You are using and/or accessing the Services which may include:   
\- Use of the Site: when You use the Site, Data about Your computer hardware and software may be automatically collected by VIOUSLY. The Data can include: Your IP address, browser type, domain names, access times and dates, and referring Site addresses.  
\- Subscription to the Platform: when subscribing to the Platform, You will transmit to VIOUSLY Your name, postal address, email address, birth date and bank details, if applicable. VIOUSLY may also collect anonymous demographic information, which is not unique to You, such as Your gender.   
\- Social media: If You access or log-in to the Site and/or Platform through a social media or other service or connect the Site and/or Platform to a social media or other service, the information VIOUSLY collects may also include Your user ID and/or user name associated with that social media service, any information or content You have permitted the social media service to share with VIOUSLY, such as Your profile picture, email address or friends lists, and any information You have made public in connection with that social media service. When You access the Site and/or Platform through social media services or when You connect the Site and/or Platform to social media services, You are authorizing VIOUSLY to collect, store, and use such information to perform the Services.

At the exclusion of Your username and Your avatar, the Data shall not be public unless shared by You within Your VIOUSLY account notably by uploading a video which contains the Data. Please keep in mind that if You directly disclose personally identifiable information or personally sensitive data, this information may be collected and used by others. Such disclosure will be made under Your sole responsibility.

The Site and/or the Platform may link to websites operated by third parties that VIOUSLY does not control. The Privacy Policy applies solely to information collected by VIOUSLY through the Site or Services and does not apply to these third party websites. Any Data You choose to disclose to these third party websites will be made under Your sole liability. VIOUSLY does not monitor, control, or endorse the Data collection or privacy practices of any third parties. VIOUSLY encourages You to review the privacy statements of websites You choose to link to from VIOUSLY so that You can understand how those websites collect, use and share Your information. 

## 3\. Use of the Data

VIOUSLY collects and uses the Data to (i) operate the Site and the Platform, (ii) to deliver the Services selected upon Your subscription to the Platform (notably any revenue sharing if applicable) and, (iii), from time to time, to inform and/or propose to You other products or services available on the Platform.

Furthermore, VIOUSLY uses the Data to provide general statistics regarding the use of the Site and the Platform such as to determine what VIOUSLY services are the most popular.

VIOUSLY may also contact You via surveys to conduct research about Your opinion of current services or of potential new services that may be offered on the Platform. 

## 4\. Data transfer

Your username and avatar as registered within the Platform will automatically be displayed to the public when You chose to upload videos onto the Platform.

VIOUSLY may, from time to time, contact You on behalf of external business partners about a particular offering that may be of interest to You. In those cases, the Data (e-mail, name, address, telephone number) will only be transferred to the third party, including without limitation certain information received from Your social media platform login, upon Your prior authorization.

VIOUSLY may also share the Data with trusted partners to help perform statistical analysis, send You email or postal mail, provide customer support, or arrange for deliveries. All such third parties are prohibited from using Your personal information except to provide these services to VIOUSLY, and they are required to maintain the strict confidentiality of the Data.

Other than set forth herein, VIOUSLY does not sell, rent or lease the Data to third parties.

Other than set forth herein, VIOUSLY does not sell, rent or lease the Data to third parties. 

## 5\. Use of Cookies/Targeted Advertising

VIOUSLY or third parties authorized by VIOUSLY (such as advertisers and analytics companies), may use tracking technology such as "cookies" to help personalize Your online experience. A cookie is a text file that is placed on Your hard disk by a web page server. Cookies cannot be used to run programs or deliver viruses to Your computer. Cookies are uniquely assigned to You, and can only be read by a web server in the domain that issued the cookie to You.

You have the ability to accept or decline cookies by indicating Your choice in the cookie banner displayed when connecting to the Site and/or the Platform. If You choose to decline cookies, You may not be able to fully experience the interactive features of the Services and/or the Site.

You can choose to limit Behavioral Advertising on the Site by accessing the following URL address: <http://www.aboutads.info/choices/> and opting-out of cookies placed by those vendors listed. After You opt-out, You will still see advertisements but the advertising may not be as relevant to Your interests. If You change Your computer, change Your browser, or delete Your cookies, You will need to renew Your opt-out. 

## 6\. Security and storage of the Data

VIOUSLY secures the Data from unauthorized access, use and/or disclosure by unauthorized third parties and ensures that will take all appropriate measures to limit the risk that it may be lost, damaged or misused.

Data is stored on secured third party servers in France. The Data is kept only as long as necessary for the purposes set out above. Upon termination of such purposes, Data is kept only for statistical and evidence purposes and shall not be used for any other reason. Once such period is expired, the Data is destroyed. 

## 7\. Your rights

You are entitled to access, correct and/or ask for the deletion of Your Data.

You can do so via Your personal Settings and account information and/or by sending a letter to the following address: VIOUSLY, 278 chaussée Fernand Forest, 59200 Tourcoing France. 

You can also opt-out of receiving announcements of certain information by following the unsubscribe instructions provided in the promotional e-mail You receive, by sending us an email to : [contact@viously.com](mailto:contact@viously.com).
